<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Yaoma Storytellers (Standalone)</name>
	<author>Zomuro</author>
	<supportedVersions><li>1.4</li></supportedVersions>
	<packageId>Zomuro.YaomaRaceStorytellers</packageId>
	<description>Residing primarily in the globular star cluster known as The Tianting, the Yaoma are a group of hermaphroditic xenohumans closely related to and otherwise visually indistinguishable from baseliners. They originated from a prosperous glitterworld, designed by the first of them: their mythologized hero-king known as Ku. From their Jade Progenitor, they have received a sacred mission to ensure greater humanity’s survival against the archotechs. Whether said directive is warranted- another story.

Among them are those that have traversed the full breadth of Yaoma cultivation, a psycho-transhumanist method for transcendence of the human mind and body. They are known as immortals. Immortals represent the most honored and powerful of the Yaoma, capable of altering the natural world with the aid of their comprehension of the Dao, a metaphysical gestalt schema managed by the Yaoma. By applying said laws with the usage of qi, the motive force of the universe, the Jade Sisters hope to stand against the transcendent machines.

Of these immortals, at least three of them have more than a passing interest in storytelling. Their experiences, understanding, and capabilities shape the tales that they tell to such an extent that natural law bends to them.

Survive their challenges, and you just may seize victory against the archotechs.

My warmest thanks go to:
Vex, for the incredible storyteller art of Farseer Fan as well as Kaiyi the Karmic;
Visandar_the_Unliving, for his heart-stopping depiction of Deathless Daji;
Gouda quiche, for his storyteller balance discussions and mod setting advice;
Feldoh, for his aid in optimizing this mod and polishing storyteller design;
Fraudecon, Argon, and Sovereign, for listening to my ramblings;
Elseud and TheCatLover366, for aiding in editing descriptions and lore;
And many others within the RimWorld community for your support!
	</description>
	
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases</downloadUrl>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>

	</modDependencies>

	
</ModMetaData>